I'll confirm another video, but once you've got a session, so this evaluation station,
I have executed in the current Windows mission, so I got a reverse connection with the same
voltage, 7, 8, and 8, 6, 7, 8.
Once you've got a session, so if you need to execute anything, if you need to execute
for example, the cobalt sick payload and administrator mode, so already you are an administrator
right side, so let me, already we have a generator the cobalt sick payload which will
be present under the features folder called antivirus.exe, let's go through that folder
see users, user, features, so let's execute the antivirus.exe, so now the cobalt sick
got another session, so you can see those in the administrator mode, we know because we executed
our antivirus.exe from the administrator high mandatory level privilege, so in the previous
video, we have learned the name to pipe impersonation on how it will work, so we know how
to interact with the how to do a user access control bypassing and we can get the medium
mandatory level to the high mandatory level of privilege, so now we are in the high mandatory
level, so there is a three kinds of privilege in the machine, so one is a user level, medium
level, high level, and the system level of privilege, so the system level is high
mandatory high privilege recon like VIP plus account, so you can do anything you can interact
with the kernel, you can interact with driver files, you can interact with anything
which in under the machine, you can do anything in the machine, there is no restriction,
no DNA access error which will be there, so you can do anything if you are in the system,
so we are implementing a name to pipe impersonation attack to bypass the privilege from high
to system level, so we already got the connection in cobalt sick, let me will interact
with that, we will go for a elevate help in a cobalt sick, cobalt sick has a mod you will
call the elevate for a privilege escalation, so here you can find elevate turn a session
and elevate contacts, it is like a privileged contact, so if I do elevate dash, ok, note it
off dash, help, yeah, so I didn't, I just give an elevate, so here is a module called the
get system via an executable run as a service, in the PSU video I have mentioned the name
to pipe impersonation, how it will, how it will going to take place, let we will use, you
can go for a token duplication attack also, you can go for a sec dash exe, I will be using
the sec dash exe, elevate, sec dash exe and you need to do the listener here, so I am choosing
the S&B RAV listener, let's do this, so you can see the be combined pipe has been open,
so it was creating an adventure, so it will create a new service, new persistence
service and it will be, it will give you the system level of privilege, ok, so now you
can see there is another, or Nikon has been given by the cobalt strike, so that was in
the system privilege, so you can give you who am I, shell, who am I slash all, great
for the results, so this is the way you can easily bypass the privilege like medium to
high level, high to system level, so this is one method and we can, we will see the
other methods in the next, next videos, so now we got a result, so you can see it's a system
mandatory level, so you can do anything, ok, if you use a name, it's a system, anti authority
system, the sit of the security identifier of the system will be this one and we can do
anything, ok, we can do anything inside the machine now, there is no restriction, no error
there, no access to any errors, nothing will be there, so you can do anything inside the
machine with this kind of privilege, ok, yep, we will learn a lot of things in privilege
installation, we will hop of this video and we will continue our discussion in the next
I'll see you guys, bye-bye.